KEYS:
subnet                register Enterprise license for the cluster
callhome              enable callhome to MinIO SUBNET
drive                 enable drive specific settings
site                  label the server and its location
api                   manage global HTTP API call specific features, such as throttling, authentication types, etc.
scanner               manage namespace scanning for usage calculation, lifecycle, healing and more
batch                 manage batch job workers and wait times
compression           enable server side compression of objects
identity_openid       enable OpenID SSO support
identity_ldap         enable LDAP SSO support
identity_tls          enable X.509 TLS certificate SSO support
identity_plugin       enable Identity Plugin via external hook
policy_plugin         enable Access Management Plugin for policy enforcement
logger_webhook        send server logs to webhook endpoints
audit_webhook         send audit logs to webhook endpoints
audit_kafka           send audit logs to kafka endpoints
notify_webhook        publish bucket notifications to webhook endpoints
notify_amqp           publish bucket notifications to AMQP endpoints
notify_kafka          publish bucket notifications to Kafka endpoints
notify_mqtt           publish bucket notifications to MQTT endpoints
notify_nats           publish bucket notifications to NATS endpoints
notify_nsq            publish bucket notifications to NSQ endpoints
notify_mysql          publish bucket notifications to MySQL databases
notify_postgres       publish bucket notifications to Postgres databases
notify_elasticsearch  publish bucket notifications to Elasticsearch endpoints
notify_redis          publish bucket notifications to Redis datastores
lambda_webhook        manage remote lambda functions
etcd                  persist IAM assets externally to etcd
browser               manage Browser HTTP specific features, such as Security headers, etc.
ilm                   manage ILM settings for expiration and transition workers
